Finding Aid for the Larry Gelbart Papers PASC.0022
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Projects
  - Motion Picture Projects
    - CHICAGO (Motion Picture Project) (Box 181, Folder 5)
      Screenplay: handwritten title page, dated September 16 1995. Draft, annotated, pp. 1-134.
    - CHICAGO (Motion Picture Project) (Box 181, Folder 6)
      Partial screenplay. No title page. Draft, September 23 1995, pp. 1-42.
    - CHICAGO (Motion Picture Project) (Box 182, Folder 1)
      Screenplay: No title page. Draft, October 9 1995, 131 p.
    - CHICAGO (Motion Picture Project) (Box 182, Folder 2)
      Screenplay: No title page. Draft, October 14 1996, 112 p.
    - CHICAGO (Motion Picture Project) (Box 182, Folder 3)
      Screenplay by Larry Gelbart. Music by John Kander. Lyrics by Fred Ebb. Based on the play by Maurine Watkins. Draft, October 16 1995, 133 p.
    - CHICAGO (Motion Picture Project) (Box 182, Folder 4)
      Screenplay by Larry Gelbart. Music by John Kander. Lyrics by Frank Ebb. Based on the play by Maurine Watkins. Revised draft, September 24 1996, annotated, 97 p.
    - CHICAGO (Motion Picture Project) (Box 182, Folder 5)
      Screenplay: No title page. Draft, October 15 1996, 113 p.
    - CITY OF ANGELS (Motion Picture Project) (Box 47, Folder 5)
      Screenplay adaptation, heavily annotated by Joe Leonards. Cover letter, June 1, 1995.
    - ECSTASY BUSINESS (THE) (Motion Picture Project) (Box 14, Folder 3)
      Manuscript of screenplay (scenes 1-290), 141 pages, n.d. - Typed script (scenes 1-274), 138 pages, heavily annotated, pages inserted, n.d.
    - ECSTASY BUSINESS (THE) (Motion Picture Project) (Box 14, Folder 4)
      Manuscript for scenes 1 through 104, 51 pages. - Typed and manuscript scenes 1 through 331, 166 pages plus inserts.
    - ECSTASY BUSINESS (THE) (Motion Picture Project) (Box 14, Folder 5)
      Handwritten notes for scenes 1 through 76 and 15 through 44. - Ms notes "Loose T.E.B.", 3 pages. - Suggested cast, 4 pages. - Unsigned letter to Voiceprint Laboratories, n.d. - 2 sets of 'scene cards'.
    - ECSTASY BUSINESS (THE) (Motion Picture Project) (Box 27, Folder 3)
      Screenplay Larry Gelbart. From the novel by Richard Condon. July 1, 1968, 138 pages. - Carbon copy marked "First Draft", dated 10 July 1968, 138 pages.
    - ECSTASY BUSINESS (THE) (Motion Picture Project) (Box 27, Folder 4)
      Carbon copy of "First Draft", 144 pages, n.d. - Synopsis, cover page dated August 1969, 27 pages, with 2-page "Background". - Partial scripts, shots 1-100, 512 pages.
    - ECSTASY BUSINESS (THE) (Motion Picture Project) (Box 27, Folder 5)
      Screenplay by Larry Gelbart, dated April 15, 1969, 138 pages.
    - ECSTASY BUSINESS (THE) (Motion Picture Project) (Box 30, Folder 1)
      Screenplay, some annotations, n.d., 145 pages.
    - ECSTASY BUSINESS (THE) (Motion Picture Project) (Box 36, Folder 1)
      Correspondence with Richard Condon related to script and production issues, 1968-1972.
    - EYE.CON (Motion Picture Project) (Box 143, Folder 10)
      Scripts by Larry Gelbart, Gary Markowitz, Denis Boiteau, and David Stansfield. Draft, no date, 124 p. - Draft, no date, 120 p.
    - FACE IS FAMILIAR (THE) (Motion Picture Project) (Box 180, Folder 6)
      Screenplay by Arthur Ross and Larry Gelbart. Marked "first draft, #3." No date. 36 p.
    - FAIR GAME (Motion Picture Project) (Box 30, Folder 2)
      Screenplay, 159 pages. includes 2-page letter to Charles K. Feldman by Stanley Shapiro, 4- 26-60.
    - FAIR GAME (Motion Picture Project) (Box 30, Folder 3)
      Screenplay, carbon copy, n.d., 146 pages.
    - FAIR GAME (Motion Picture Project) (Box 30, Folder 4)
      Screenplay by Larry Gelbart, September 25, 1961 (Prod. # 8593), 170 pages. - Loose pages (revisions). - Handwritten notes, total of 9 pages.
    - FIRST ROW CENTER (Motion Picture Project) (Box 180, Folder 7)
      Film treatment by Richard Joseph and Cary Pepper, Property of Larry Gelbart, Allan Pepper and Stanley Snadowsky, no date, 65 p. - Story memorandum, by Sherry Coben, no date, 11 p.
    - FLINSTONES (THE) (Motion Picture Project) (Box 189, Folder 13)
      "The Flinstones Conversion." Packet of notes re: possibility of Gelbart adapting "The Flinstones" into a live-action motion picture, 6/1/92, 5p.
    - FRANK (Motion Picture Project) (Box 164, Folder 4)
      Handwritten notes regarding scripts. Summer 1993. Correspondence.
    - FRANK (Motion Picture Project) (Box 168, Folder 5)
      Script by Andy Breckman and revised by Larry Gelbart. Draft, April 4 1995, 120 p.
    - FRANK (Motion Picture Project) (Box 168, Folder 6)
      Script. No title page. Draft, March 30 1995, annotated, 119 p.
    - FRANK (Motion Picture Project) (Box 168, Folder 7)
      Cover letter w/ revision pages & an article (11/17/93). - Outline, no date, 7 p. - Breakdowns (43) annotated: n.d., 2/15, 1/30/95 & 1/17/95. - Pretitles sequence, 2/28/95, annotated, 24 p.
    - FRANK (Motion Picture Project) (Box 168, Folder 8)
      Notes by Jerry Zucker with cover letter, 07/29/96. - Notes by Larry Gelbart, 05/08/96, some handwritten, 5 p. - Outline, 11/27/95, 16 p.
    - FRANK (Motion Picture Project) (Box 168, Folder 9)
      Script. No title page. Draft, 03/29/95, annotated, 110 p.
    - FRANK (Motion Picture Project) (Box 168, Folder 10)
      Script, Draft, 03/13/94, with laser printer cover page, 131 p.
    - FRANK (Motion Picture Project) (Box 168, Folder 11)
      Revisions and correspondence re: revision with Zucker Productions, August 1993.
    - FRANK (Motion Picture Project) (Box 168, Folder 12)
      Script marked "Final 2nd draft, April 15 1995," 120 p.
    - FRANK (Motion Picture Project) (Box 169, Folder 1)
      Script [missing title page.] No date. Annotated. 116 pages.
    - FRANK (Motion Picture Project) (Box 169, Folder 2)
      Script [missing title page.] Draft, March 3 1995, annotated, 118 p.
    - FRANK (Motion Picture Project) (Box 169, Folder 3)
      Script. Annotated, no date, 120 p.
    - FRANK (Motion Picture Project) (Box 169, Folder 4)
      Script by Andy Breckman and revised by Larry Gelbart. Revised draft, March 14 1994, 127 p.
    - FRANK (Motion Picture Project) (Box 169, Folder 5)
      Script [with laser printer title page], revised draft, 02/14/94, 14 p.
    - FRANK (Motion Picture Project) (Box 169, Folder 6)
      Step outlines, 3 items. One is annotated. None are dated.
    - FRANK (Motion Picture Project) (Box 169, Folder 7)
      Outline with some dialogue: - Draft, 01/10/94, 19 p. - Draft, 11/22/93, 23 p. - Draft, no date, 13 p.
    - FRANK (Motion Picture Project) (Box 169, Folder 8)
      Outlines beginning with the murder investigation. Draft, 01/11/94, annotated, 17 p. - Draft, 01/10/94, annotated, 16 p. - Draft, 02/07/94, annotated, 24 p.
    - FRANK (Motion Picture Project) (Box 169, Folder 9)
      Breakdowns (10 items), dated January 31 - February 28, 1995. Some have cover letters attached.
    - FRANK (Motion Picture Project) (Box 169, Folder 10)
      Script by Larry Gelbart [with laser printer cover sheet]. Draft, 03/06/94, 131 p.
    - FRANK (Motion Picture Project) (Box 170, Folder 1)
      Script by Larry Gelbart. Draft, March 19 1995, 80 p.
    - FRANK (Motion Picture Project) (Box 170, Folder 2)
      Incomplete scripts by Larry Gelbart. Drafts dated March 4 - 12, 1995. First act only.
    - FRANK (Motion Picture Project) (Box 180, Folder 12)
      Screenplay. No title page. No date. Heavily annotated. 122 pages.
    - FRANK (Motion Picture Project) (Box 180, Folder 13)
      Scene breakdowns (3): - March 2, 1995, 27 pages. - March 4, 1995, annotated, 28 pages. - November 13, 1995, 7 pages.
    - GOING, GOING - GONE! (Motion Picture Project) (Box 144, Folder 7)
      Registration of idea with WGA, April 4 1977. - Story idea, 2 p.
    - HADRIAN VII (Motion Picture Project) (Box 155, Folder 4)
      Screenplay outlines, handwritten, 3 version, n.d. & dated October 1 1976, and notes, total pgs 17 - Correspondence regarding adaptation of the novel into a screenplay, July-Sept. 1976, Oct, 1978.
    - HANNIE CAULDER (1972) (Box 48, Folder 1)
      First draft screenplay [by Larry Gelbart and David Haft], n.d. 97 pages. - Copy of unsigned and undated contract, Tigon Film Productions, Ltd. London and 2 accompanying letters, November 1970.
    - HEARTS OF THE WEST (MGM, 1974) (Box 43, Folder 5)
      Screenplay by Rob Thompson, 126 pages, dated 09/09/74.
    - HOTEL ROYALE (Motion Picture Project) (Box 103, Folder 3)
      Script by Larry Gelbart. Handwritten Rev. First draft, dated 1980, 230 p.
    - HOTEL ROYALE (Motion Picture Project) (Box 103, Folder 4)
      Script by Larry Gelbart. Handwritten draft, titled "Clicks," dated June 1983, 69 p.
    - HOTEL ROYALE (Motion Picture Project) (Box 103, Folder 5)
      Script by Larry Gelbart. Handwritten first draft, 11/30/79.
    - HOTEL ROYALE (Motion Picture Project) (Box 103, Folder 6)
      Script by Larry Gelbart. Handwritten, Act III, n.d., pages 174 - 214.
    - HOTEL ROYALE (Motion Picture Project) (Box 103, Folder 7)
      Script by Larry Gelbart. Handwritten draft, no date.
    - HOTEL ROYALE (Motion Picture Project) (Box 104, Folder 1)
      Xerox of manuscript titled "Roadrunner," no author, no date, some annotations, approx. 500 pages in length.
    - HOTEL ROYALE (Motion Picture Project) (Box 104, Folder 2)
      Interview with Ian Brody regarding time in Cambodia. June 15, 1979.
    - HOTEL ROYALE (Motion Picture Project) (Box 104, Folder 3)
      Interview with Richard Dudman regarding time in Cambodia. May 21, 1979.
    - HOTEL ROYALE (Motion Picture Project) (Box 104, Folder 4)
      Interview between Larry Gelbart and Al Rockoff. No date. Annotated.
    - HOTEL ROYALE (Motion Picture Project) (Box 104, Folder 5)
      Interview with Justin Adams. No date. 80 pages.
    - HOTEL ROYALE (Motion Picture Project) (Box 104, Folder 6)
      Interview with Burt Okuley regarding Foreign Correspondents Club in Hong Kong. No date. 63 pages.
    - HOTEL ROYALE (Motion Picture Project) (Box 105, Folder 1)
      Interview between Larry Gelbart and Robert Sam Anson regarding time in Cambodia. Dated May 2nd.
    - HOTEL ROYALE (Motion Picture Project) (Box 105, Folder 2)
      Interview with San Bun Chhun regarding time with NBC news in Cambodia.
    - HOTEL ROYALE (Motion Picture Project) (Box 105, Folder 3)
      Interviews (2 items) with Kate Webb. No date.
    - HOTEL ROYALE (Motion Picture Project) (Box 105, Folder 4)
      Interview with Bert Quint. Dated September 12, 1979. 69 pages.
    - HOTEL ROYALE (Motion Picture Project) (Box 105, Folder 5)
      Synopsis titled "Asian Report." Ideas for a film, ala M*A*S*H about a group of reporters living in the same hotel during the Vietnam war. Compiled by Julie Fisher Associates. No date.
    - HOTEL ROYALE (Motion Picture Project) (Box 105, Folder 6)
      Interviews (2 items) - Hanny-Howell, June 7, 1979, annotated, 29 pages. - Howell-Brady, June 8, 1979, 54 pages.
    - HOTEL ROYALE (Motion Picture Project) (Box 105, Folder 7)
      Interviews (2 items) with Kevin Buckley. June 1979.
    - HOTEL ROYALE (Motion Picture Project) (Box 105, Folder 8)
      Interview with Neil Davis. June 13, 1979. 71 pages.
    - HOTEL ROYALE (Motion Picture Project) (Box 105, Folder 9)
      Interview between Mike Morrow and Marvin Farkus. No date. 62 pages.
    - HOTEL ROYALE (Motion Picture Project) (Box 105, Folder 10)
      Interview with Tiziano Terzani. June 10, 1979. 26 pages.
    - HOTEL ROYALE (Motion Picture Project) (Box 105, Folder 11)
      Excerpt. By James Willwerth. "Messages from Washington." 61 pages.
    - HOTEL ROYALE (Motion Picture Project) (Box 105, Folder 12)
      Interview with Peter Collins. June 10, 1979. 39 pages.
    - HOTEL ROYALE (Motion Picture Project) (Box 105, Folder 13)
      Manuscript by Larry Gelbart. Incomplete. Dated 1973. Annotated.
    - HOTEL ROYALE (Motion Picture Project) (Box 106, Folder 1)
      Script by Larry Gelbart. titled "Cambodia Project." First draft, 11/30/79, 217 p.
    - HOTEL ROYALE (Motion Picture Project) (Box 106, Folder 2)
      Script by Larry Gelbart. titled "Cambodia Project." Revised First draft ("Part Three"), 02/15/80, 190 p.
    - HOTEL ROYALE (Motion Picture Project) (Box 106, Folder 3)
      Script by Larry Gelbart. titled "Cambodia Project." First revised draft, 03/01/80, annotated, 147 p.
    - HOTEL ROYALE (Motion Picture Project) (Box 106, Folder 4)
      Script by Larry Gelbart. Second Draft, June 1980, annotated, 147 p.
    - HOTEL ROYALE (Motion Picture Project) (Box 106, Folder 5)
      Letter, dated 02/22/83, from Tom Mount to Arthur Penn regarding the progress of the script. - Script by Larry Gelbart, no date, 129 p.
    - HOTEL ROYALE (Motion Picture Project) (Box 106, Folder 6)
      Script titled "Clicks." By Larry Gelbart. Dated 06/15/83, annotated by Arthur Penn, 129 p.
    - HOTEL ROYALE (Motion Picture Project) (Box 107, Folder 1)
      Script titled "Clicks", n.d., annotated, 228 pages. Written by Larry Gelbart.
    - HOTEL ROYALE (Motion Picture Project) (Box 107, Folder 2)
      Script. Draft, n.d., annotated, 185 p.
    - HOTEL ROYALE (Motion Picture Project) (Box 107, Folder 3)
      Script. Draft, n.d., annotated, pp. 2-205
    - HOTEL ROYALE (Motion Picture Project) (Box 107, Folder 4)
      Notes. Includes handwritten note: "Project finally abandoned because of the film The Killing Fields," 02/26/85.
    - HOTEL ROYALE (Motion Picture Project) (Box 107, Folder 5)
      Photograph. Potential location to be used as the Hotel Royal.
    - HOTEL ROYALE (Motion Picture Project) (Box 107, Folder 6)
      Correspondence between Larry Gelbart and Jules Fisher, dated 8/20/79 - 12/31/80. Includes Asian report notes (08/20/79). 5 items.
    - HOTEL ROYALE (Motion Picture Project) (Box 107, Folder 7)
      Two copies of contracts between Columbia Pictures and Larry Gelbart Enterprises. Both signed by Larry Gelbart. Dated June 16 - September 11, 1979.
    - HOTEL ROYALE (Motion Picture Project) (Box 107, Folder 8)
      Correspondence dated 7/31/79 - 2/4/81. Regarding the potential sale of the script, primarily legal. approx. 15 items.
    - HOTEL ROYALE (Motion Picture Project) (Box 131, Folder 3)
      Script by Larry Gelbart, June 10, 1980, 129 pages.
    - HOTEL ROYALE (Motion Picture Project) (Box 191, Folder 12)
      Newspaper articles regarding Vietnam war and Cambodia, May 1975. Approx. 50 items.
    - JAZZ BABIES (Motion Picture Project) (Box 146, Folder 2)
      Scripts by Larry Gelbart. Handwritten third draft, July 22, 1985, 2 copies, 115 and 131 p.
    - JAZZ BABIES (Motion Picture Project) (Box 146, Folder 3)
      Handwritten step outline for fourth draft, n.d., 50 p.
    - JAZZ BABIES (Motion Picture Project) (Box 146, Folder 4)
      Script by Larry Gelbart. Handwritten fourth draft, December 30.,1985, 123 p.
    - JAZZ BABIES (Motion Picture Project) (Box 146, Folder 5)
      Script by Larry Gelbart. Handwritten first draft, marked "Begun 6/13/84, Finished 7/14/84," 126 p.
    - JAZZ BABIES (Motion Picture Project) (Box 146, Folder 6)
      Handwritten revised outline for first revised draft, December 27 1984 - February 1985, 76 p.
    - JAZZ BABIES (Motion Picture Project) (Box 146, Folder 7)
      Letter to Carla regarding duplications of scripts (8/20/84). - Handwritten notes, marked "Begun May 1 1984."
    - JAZZ BABIES (Motion Picture Project) (Box 146, Folder 8)
      Telegram regarding script (07/01/86). - Handwritten rough outline for first draft, "begun May 1 1984 [and] finished June 8 1984," 75 p.
    - JAZZ BABIES (Motion Picture Project) (Box 146, Folder 9)
      Script by Larry Gelbart. Handwritten second draft, February 27, 1985.
    - JAZZ BABIES (Motion Picture Project) (Box 146, Folder 10)
      Handwritten notes for 3rd draft, "begun 6/4/85."
    - JAZZ BABIES (Motion Picture Project) (Box 148, Folder 1)
      Script by Larry Gelbart. Draft, 09/22/87, 105 p.
    - JAZZ BABIES (Motion Picture Project) (Box 148, Folder 2)
      Script by Larry Gelbart. Draft, July 17, 1995, 105 p.
    - JAZZ BABIES (Motion Picture Project) (Box 148, Folder 3)
      Script by Larry Gelbart. Fifth draft, July 1, 1986, 123 p.
    - JAZZ BABIES (Motion Picture Project) (Box 148, Folder 4)
      Script by Larry Gelbart. Fourth draft, July 22, 1985, annotated, 133 p.
    - JAZZ BABIES (Motion Picture Project) (Box 148, Folder 5)
      Script by Larry Gelbart. Typed first draft, July 7, 1984, 126 p.
    - JAZZ BABIES (Motion Picture Project) (Box 148, Folder 6)
      Script by Larry Gelbart. First draft, July 8, 1984, annotated, 128 p.
    - JAZZ BABIES (Motion Picture Project) (Box 148, Folder 7)
      Script by Larry Gelbart. Typed original, first draft, August 21, 1984, 122 p.
    - JAZZ BABIES (Motion Picture Project) (Box 148, Folder 8)
      Script by Larry Gelbart. First draft, August 23, 1984, heavily annotated, 122 p.
    - JAZZ BABIES (Motion Picture Project) (Box 149, Folder 1)
      Script by Larry Gelbart. Typed original. Second draft, February 27, 1985, 103 p.
    - JAZZ BABIES (Motion Picture Project) (Box 149, Folder 2)
      Script by Larry Gelbart. Third draft, July 22, 1985, 135 p.
    - JAZZ BABIES (Motion Picture Project) (Box 149, Folder 3)
      Outline for 4th draft, first through thirty-first scene, by Larry Gelbart September 30, 1985, 50 p.
    - JAZZ BABIES (Motion Picture Project) (Box 149, Folder 4)
      Script by Larry Gelbart. Draft, December 30,1985, 119 p.
    - JAZZ BABIES (Motion Picture Project) (Box 149, Folder 5)
      Scene breakdown for July 1, 1986 draft, 6 p.
    - JAZZ BABIES (Motion Picture Project) (Box 149, Folder 6)
      Scripts by Larry Gelbart. Draft, July 1, 1986, heavily annotated, 118 p. - Draft, same date, somewhat annotated, 123 p.
    - JAZZ BABIES (Motion Picture Project) (Box 149, Folder 7)
      Script by Larry Gelbart. Sixth draft, September 20, 1987, annotated, 98 p.
    - JAZZ BABIES (Motion Picture Project) (Box 149, Folder 8)
      Script by Larry Gelbart. Draft, September 22, 1987, annotated, 123 p.
    - JAZZ BABIES (Motion Picture Project) (Box 150, Folder 1)
      Notes for fifth draft, May 13, 1986.
    - JAZZ BABIES (Motion Picture Project) (Box 150, Folder 2)
      Script, incomplete draft, handwritten, 1986.
    - JAZZ BABIES (Motion Picture Project) (Box 150, Folder 3)
      Handwritten notes, May 1987.
    - JAZZ BABIES (Motion Picture Project) (Box 151, Folder 1)
      Letter to Larry Gelbart from Norman Jewison (09/24/85) with attached comments regarding Third Draft. - Letter from Norman Jewison (10/01/86) with attached letter regarding draft.
    - JAZZ BABIES (Motion Picture Project) (Box 151, Folder 2)
      Casting lists, March 1986.
    - JAZZ BABIES (Motion Picture Project) (Box 151, Folder 3)
      Articles as research for film, particularly women as Jazz performers.
    - KILL-IN (Motion Picture Project) (Box 58, Folder 1)
      "The Assassin", novel by Lester Taube. (typescript). Heavily annotated.
    - KILL-IN (Motion Picture Project) (Box 58, Folder 2)
      Screenplay by Larry Gelbart. Based on "The Assassin" by Lester Taube. 2 copies of First Draft, [127 and 129 pages], n.d.
    - KILL-IN (Motion Picture Project) (Box 58, Folder 3)
      Screenplays, first draft, dated 08/14/72, 120 pages. - First Draft, n.d., 136 pages. - One page (scenes 240-243) handwritten.
    - LITTLE ME (Motion Picture Project) (Box 48, Folder 8)
      Handwritten drafts, in 2 folders.
    - LITTLE ME (Motion Picture Project) (Box 58, Folder 4)
      Screenplay, no author, no date, marked "Avco Embassy Picture Corp," 145 p.
    - LITTLE ME (Motion Picture Project) (Box 58, Folder 5)
      Screenplay by Larry Gelbart. No date. 156 pages.
    - M*A*S*H (20th Century-Fox, 1971) (Box 78, Folder 6)
      Screenplay: Written by Ring Lardner Jr. Based on novel by Richard Hooker. Dated 02/26/69, 141 p.
    - MOVIE MOVIE (Warner Bros., 1978) (Box 48, Folder 2)
      Handwritten draft and notes for script. No date.
    - MOVIE MOVIE (Warner Bros., 1978) (Box 89, Folder 4)
      Script by Larry Gelbart. Handwritten draft, annotated, 10/10/77.
    - MOVIE MOVIE (Warner Bros., 1978) (Box 89, Folder 5)
      Handwritten "Movie Movie Log Log," Notes as explanation for screenplay, 11/28/78. - "Story Behind Movie Movie," 11/12/78. - Newsreel script.
    - MOVIE MOVIE (Warner Bros., 1978) (Box 89, Folder 7)
      Record album lyrics. Some typed, some hand written. Dated 1979. 21 items.
    - MOVIE MOVIE (Warner Bros., 1978) (Box 95, Folder 1)
      Correspondence, dated 10/21/82 - 4/16/79. 40 items.
    - MOVIE MOVIE (Warner Bros., 1978) (Box 95, Folder 2)
      Scripts by Larry Gelbart & Sheldon Keller. Rev draft titled "Double Feature," 06/13/77, annotated, 136 p. - Partial script, annotated.
    - MOVIE MOVIE (Warner Bros., 1978) (Box 95, Folder 3)
      Script by Larry Gelbart and Sheldon Keller. First draft, titled "Double Feature," dated 09/15/76, 136 p.
    - MOVIE MOVIE (Warner Bros., 1978) (Box 95, Folder 4)
      Scripts by Larry Gelbart and Shelden Keller First draft, dated 06/01/76, annotated, 67 p. - Typed draft, 06/01/76, annotated, 69 p.
    - MOVIE MOVIE (Warner Bros., 1978) (Box 95, Folder 5)
      Press Clippings, dated 1978, including reviews.
    - MOVIE MOVIE (Warner Bros., 1978) (Box 95, Folder 6)
      Press packet materials: transcripts of broadcast reviews, reviews, interviews, general publicity information, 1978.
    - MOVIE MOVIE (Warner Bros., 1978) (Box 95, Folder 7)
      Script by Larry Gelbart. Draft, titled "Double Feature," annotated, 147 p., no date.
    - MOVIE MOVIE (Warner Bros., 1978) (Box 95, Folder 8)
      Script by Larry Gelbart and Sheldon Keller. Revised draft, dated 07/01/77, annotated.
    - MOVIE MOVIE (Warner Bros., 1978) (Box 95, Folder 9)
      Publicity stills (8 items); Clippings (2 items).
    - MOVIE MOVIE (Warner Bros., 1978) (Box 96, Folder 1)
      Scripts by Larry Gelbart and Sheldon Keller. - Rev. draft, labeled "Master," 06/13/76, annotated, 122 p. - Rev. draft, 06/13/77, 122 p.
    - MOVIE MOVIE (Warner Bros., 1978) (Box 96, Folder 2)
      Scripts by Larry Gelbart and Sheldon Keller. Typed draft, no date, annotated, 125 p. - Revised pages, 09/14/77, annotated.
    - MOVIE MOVIE (Warner Bros., 1978) (Box 96, Folder 3)
      Scripts by Larry Gelbart & Sheldon Keller. Rev. partial draft, 09/14/77, annotated, pp. 61-121. - Rev draft, 07/01/77, annotated, pp. 3-121. - Revised pages, annotations.
    - MOVIE MOVIE (Warner Bros., 1978) (Box 96, Folder 4)
      Shooting schedule, dated 11/15/77, marked "start date 11/17/77, finish date 1/15/78". - Music and lyrics for "Baxters Beauties of 1933" segment.
    - MOVIE MOVIE (Warner Bros., 1978) (Box 96, Folder 5)
      Revision of "Dynamite Hands", dated 9/7/77, pp. 2-45. (2 copies) - Continuity for "Torching for Bill" segment, 8 p.
    - MOVIE MOVIE (Warner Bros., 1978) (Box 96, Folder 6)
      Research for "Dynamite Hands" segment. Dated 08/22/77. Compiled by de Forest Research.
    - MOVIE MOVIE (Warner Bros., 1978) (Box 96, Folder 7)
      Lyrics: I Just Need the Girl, 12/7/77. - What a Cutie, 12/12/77.
    - MOVIE MOVIE (Warner Bros., 1978) (Box 133, Folder 1)
      Correspondence regarding legal issues with the film. 1975-1977.
    - MOVIE MOVIE (Warner Bros., 1978) (Box 198, Folder 6)
      Exhibitor presskit, including reviews, articles and illustrations.
    - MOVIE MOVIE 2 (Motion Picture Project) (Box 89, Folder 3)
      Handwritten script by Larry Gelbart. Part one, 08/01/78, 76 p. - Part two, 06/20/78, 81 p.
    - MOVIE MOVIE 2 (Motion Picture Project) (Box 89, Folder 6)
      Handwritten breakdown of scenes with notes, annotated and illustrated. - Typed first draft, August 1 1978. - Typed revised pages.
    - MOVIE MOVIE 2 (Motion Picture Project) (Box 96, Folder 8)
      Script. Typed first draft, 08/01/78, annotated, 133 p.